<contentList>
    <content contentuid="h142c3612g35d8g4dc8g83dbg0fdc7facec7b">Thank you for playing Epic Encounters!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It appears you have have correctly installed the mod, enjoy your adventures!</content>
    <content contentuid="h009289e1gdc60g4794g8283g81e4af485ecb">Level [1]: Boosts Initiative by 3, Damage and Chance to hit by 5%.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h00a9f88eg348ag4d7cgb38fgda136fae29fd">Storm</content>
    <content contentuid="h01dd61c8gd2fdg426fgbd15g4b3f66ab663f">Grandstander</content>
    <content contentuid="h02f7d745ga9dfg46fbga65ag114bd1bb3bb9"/>
    <content contentuid="h08d17d54gf579g43ebga0a6gbf74ad1fc133">Take caution to protect your resurrected companions, as they will return in a greatly weakened state for a short time.</content>
    <content contentuid="h0a195ac5g322fg4d07g9da9gbf8d88089601"/>
    <content contentuid="h0d26623bg41deg477cgb26dg1a1354e16864">Don't be so quick to put the moves on your enemies; in Epic Encounters charmed enemies will become enraged after they realize you've charmed them, making them immune to further charms and just very upset in general.</content>
    <content contentuid="h0e2dc6e9g5a11g45bagbde6gaa8a03fd1667">[1] allows you to perform &quot;[1] reactions&quot; each round. Additionally, Predator gives you an extra [2]% chance to evade hits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;You start combat with zero Predator reactions, but recover 1 at the start of each turn, storing up to 3.&lt;br&gt;Predator reactions trigger whenever an enemy within weapon range becomes Stunned, Crippled, Knocked Down, Blind, or Feared.&lt;br&gt;You may only perform this reaction if you would not be prevented from attacking and it is not your turn&lt;br&gt;You can only perform Predator reactions as fast as you can normally attack.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h0f084e60g8d2fg40e5g998dg5fba94c785fa">To examine a character, open the Action menu and use Examine. The higher your Loremaster skill, the more detailed the info you get.</content>
    <content contentuid="h11065363gf07eg4764ga834g9eeab569ceec"/>
    <content contentuid="h114e624bg975bg4de2g86f7ge749ca34e1b4">While wielding two weapons, they will suffer a 30% damage penalty. To reduce this, invest points in Dual Wielding.</content>
    <content contentuid="h13b41369g85b4g4897ga277g55b06c779b4b">Occultist</content>
    <content contentuid="h1454af55gdb0fg4d6fgbde1g8235fa16d980">[1] grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Charm&lt;/font&gt;.</content>
    <content contentuid="h164edc34g94fbg4957ga636gbfbdea39fc72">&lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Win&lt;/font&gt; a series of &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Rock, Paper, Scissors&lt;/font&gt; matches to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;convince&lt;/font&gt; the other party. Put points in &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Bard&lt;/font&gt; to gain an &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;advantage&lt;/font&gt;. Press [IE_UIEndTurn] to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;skip&lt;/font&gt; the RPS.</content>
    <content contentuid="h1766a487g183cg47a2g9827g180666c92fcd">failed. Loremaster level too low.</content>
    <content contentuid="h17d48c1fg3287g4be8g900cgddfe62b2a4c9">[1] causes your Crushing damage to daze targets, reducing their initiative by 3 for 2 turns. This effect may stack up to a maximum of -12 initiative. Additionally, your damage with crushing weapons is increased by [2]%.</content>
    <content contentuid="h186ab59agf502g4c67gb91ag3a9be07b066e">&lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Win&lt;/font&gt; a series of &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Rock, Paper, Scissors&lt;/font&gt; matches to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;convince&lt;/font&gt; the other party. Put points in &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Bard&lt;/font&gt; to gain an &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;advantage&lt;/font&gt;. Hold [IE_UIEndTurn] to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;skip&lt;/font&gt; the RPS.</content>
    <content contentuid="h197b2667g7a60g45bdga915gd30140660322"/>
    <content contentuid="h19edfe6agf4a4g4f62g9341gd2b41127f1a1">Drain Willpower Scroll</content>
    <content contentuid="h200df626g931dg461cgb791ga8cb929fe038">Level [1]: Boosts Initiative by 7, Damage by 10%, Chance to hit by 10%, Critical Chance by 3%, and Armour by 6.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h278b2bccg1afcg4314gbfcbgb10105ebc12b">Whenever you kill a target within 4 meters of you, you instantly gain 35% of your turn action points. Also, when resurrected, you revive with full health.</content>
    <content contentuid="h285c0c44g7cf1g43deg8ec7g6d6e9b7deba0">Pickpocketing</content>
    <content contentuid="h2b97bbedga210g46c7ga762g74ab945b27f5">[1] grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Freezing&lt;/font&gt;.</content>
    <content contentuid="h2d16522egbb21g4991g8302g354718ff9b0d">Lockpicking level too low</content>
    <content contentuid="h2f9ec5acgbcbeg45b8g8058gee363e6875d5">Lucky Charm</content>
    <content contentuid="h32afab3bg46b9g40dfg8a3egdcb1acf960d3">Epic Encounters detected!&lt;br&gt;Ensure that it is activated in the Mods menu. Good luck and thanks for playing!</content>
    <content contentuid="h34f27a9bg5a6eg4421g9d15g8b83d498124d">Attacking guards in a city is one of the funniest ways to kill people.</content>
    <content contentuid="h3587f7f0g8f0dg4418g9f99g2e5b53e27fa9">Drain Willpower Skillbook</content>
    <content contentuid="h3a60d865gc078g4d09g9f3fg693d17fe04a8">[1] allows you to perform melee Attacks of Opportunity against attackers that miss you, or whom you block. Also, you no longer suffer a defense penalty when flanked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;You cannot retaliate against attackers who are out of your reach.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h3d72869dgfda9g4ddega996gc78970aa3436">[1] causes your Rot damage to apply Delerium, the effects of which increase with your Tenebrium skill. Additionally, grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Mute&lt;/font&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;a6a6a6&quot;&gt;Tenebrium 4: -2 Initiative.&lt;br&gt;Tenebrium 5: 15% chance to Curse.&lt;br&gt;Tenebrium 6: Curse chance to 30%.&lt;br&gt;Tenebrium 7: Curse chance to 45%.&lt;br&gt;Tenebrium 8: -1 Willpower.&lt;br&gt;Tenebrium 9: Initiative to -4, and -3 AP Recovery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each level also conveys the effects of previous levels.</content>
    <content contentuid="h3feab349ge27ag40a8gb043gc7a4f45aac39">Revisit every skill! Epic Encounters reworks the original skills, so give those subpar spells another chance and see if they can't catch your fancy.</content>
    <content contentuid="h402b1bfeg3f47g43c5ga481g2fddcd3e6972">Be careful when saving up Chain bonus- if you miss an attack, you'll lose two stacks, and if you aren't invisible or sneaking when your turn starts, you'll lose it all!</content>
    <content contentuid="h41684539g341cg48d5g9d85gf6889e7dab01"/>
    <content contentuid="h41bff6f7gd7d6g43f1g9b36g6bec5876893d">[1] grants +20 Defense rating. Additionally, you gain a [2]% Blocking Chance while dual wielding.</content>
    <content contentuid="h42e92daagb98eg4c1bga774gf6e395a08e25">[1] improves your armour rating, decreases movement penalties from equipment worn, increases your Poison Resistance, and improves your maximum resistances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;Each level grants +3 armour rating, +1% to all maximum resistances, +5% to Poison Resistance, and reduces movement penalty by 20%. Movement penalty cannot be reduced past 100%, but for levels beyond 5th, an extra +1% to all maximum resistances is awarded.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h44eff09aga11bg4b03ga06eg28f944bc1267">Sneaking ability improves your movement speed while sneaking, shrinks NPC sight cones, and increases the power of backstabs. Every level of Sneaking past 2 increases your backstab multiplier by 0.3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pickpocketing allows you to pickpocket more intelligent and perceptive characters. Additionally, it determines the weight and value that can be stolen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lockpicking influences the complexity of locks you can pick, and the speed at which you can do it.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h455eb073g28abg4f3bgae9dga8a592a30cdb">Telekinesis</content>
    <content contentuid="h4899733eg21edg4bebg9e5ag2e04e1d6b104">We hope you enjoy experiencing Epic Encounters at least as much as we enjoyed creating it. :)</content>
    <content contentuid="h49426677g68f9g4467g947cg68fad9de4af8">[1] gives you [2]% x Soldier extra Vitality. Additionally, grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Petrification&lt;/font&gt; at Soldier 5.</content>
    <content contentuid="h49692c5cg5a16g4d32gbc79g7e5a30f7c42f">Epic Encounters reworks Charisma into the new ability, Bard. With its awesome new reactions you don't have to feel bad about picking it to win arguments anymore!</content>
    <content contentuid="h4a5037bcg4deeg44a1g962dg65fc33ecf7b5">[1] grants the ability to detect invisible or sneaking enemies at the start and end of your turn. Also gives you a +[2] Perception bonus for detecting traps and secrets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;Your Perception score determines how far away you can spot hidden enemies, and how likely you are to spot them. It becomes more difficult to spot targets that are further away, as well those that are stealthy or hidden with powerful magic. Blindness radically lowers the chance of revealing enemies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2m range for each point of Perception above 5, maximum of 20m.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h4ba4db73gc13fg42f0g9926g528945bccb0a">[1] grants +5% Critical Chance. Additionally, your grenade throws will never miss again.</content>
    <content contentuid="h4c891442g3b79g4dbeg906fgf8eeffcf60df">Relentless</content>
    <content contentuid="h4e1c39f2g2f37g433egb842g661f748ad836">Level [1]: Boosts Initiative by 5, Damage by 5%, Chance to hit by 10% and Critical Chance by 3%.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h50116f77g1be8g4cabg8c9eg97ce9b755773"/>
    <content contentuid="h509221cag2369g4e91g928egdd4dfaf65484">In Epic Encounters, wielding a dagger allows a character to build Chain from striking enemies; you can gain two per turn and up to five total. Save up your Chain to use with Chain Finishers for powerful bonus effects!</content>
    <content contentuid="h50c7cd82gbd70g4e37g9cbbgdabc2c83e588">Level [1]: Boosts Initiative by 12, Damage by 15%, Chance to hit by 15%, Critical Chance by 5%, Armour Rating by 16, Grants Immunity to Fear, and adds +1 to Willpower and Grit.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h50ccd3ebg9a48g43fdgacccg51d87e776671">[1] grants you 1 additional point of Strength and doubles the amount of weight you can carry. Additionally, grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Weak&lt;/font&gt; with Soldier 5.</content>
    <content contentuid="h50e2c4d3g1072g4987g9e3eg4f9e2e3df144">Level [1]: Boosts damage and chance to hit by 5%.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h51f73b3dg4796g45c5gad16gf22583c42e7e">To examine a character, hover over them and hit [IE_ToggleInfo]. The higher your Metamind skill, the more detailed the info you get.</content>
    <content contentuid="h52a9b492gfa8fg488dgb459g5e5bd0c455a3">The higher your Metamind score, the heavier the items you can telepathically lift, and the farther you can move them. Additionally, more information about enemies is revealed to you with a greater Metamind level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To identify, use an Identifying Glass on the item you want to identify.</content>
    <content contentuid="h5542b809g8479g405ag90e9g382e7b7e5e41">No one has more friends than the man with many Metamind points!&lt;br&gt;Epic Encounters groups Loremaster and Telekinesis into this single ability so you can grab stuff from a distance while you check stuff from a distance.</content>
    <content contentuid="h56a42032g5e88g481cgb162gaf64bb670d6b">[1] improves your saving throws against effects which directly assault the body, or test your physical wellness and perseverance.</content>
    <content contentuid="h56b21dd3g7d43g4de8gbe58ge0e7ad8f84f1">[1] allows a character to backstab with daggers, knives, rondels and rapiers. Higher Sneaking can increase the damage of your backstabs.</content>
    <content contentuid="h56ecda94gd278g462egad54g6ac9a4d10441">You found an &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;unidentified&lt;/font&gt; item. &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Identify&lt;/font&gt; it with an &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;identifying glass&lt;/font&gt;, or pay a &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;merchant&lt;/font&gt; to do so for you. You or the merchant will need enough points in &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Lore Master&lt;/font&gt; to do so.</content>
    <content contentuid="h59ad7cccg3af7g4adfg8ad0g516a6030a490">Keep your eyes sharp in those shiny new environs- you might find some hidden loot!</content>
    <content contentuid="h5b140f6egc7f4g4257gb76fg3084072b8e48">Diversify your disables! Epic Encounters imposes a two for every five turns limit on most effects that completely disable an enemy.</content>
    <content contentuid="h608446ceg3e42g4521gb07ag5597bb01b5a6">To the favored ones; to my friends: Facepalm, In and Out, Sleep, I am Disappoint--thanks for the memories.</content>
    <content contentuid="h647121a0g5bb9g4541g87f8g1ea36fc12b09">Perception is great! In Epic Encounters Perception has been greatly improved, and is essential for any character hoping to score critical strikes.&lt;br&gt;You can even add on the Hyperacuity talent to detect hidden enemies!</content>
    <content contentuid="h653df73ag9464g423fgad5ag09d19dbd8ad4">[1] lowers your damage by 10%, but boosts non-magical attacks by [2]% against opponents with Slowed, Crippled or Knocked Down.</content>
    <content contentuid="h6658a3ccg94d7g459ag95e2g2acf2d4e021f">Bard</content>
    <content contentuid="h67fc2341g6949g4283g8eb3g2566cbfcda83">Iron Will</content>
    <content contentuid="h6a4f7786g3c96g419bgb023g8cd0d25ee9b3">Predator</content>
    <content contentuid="h6bf7caf0g7756g443bg926dg1ee5975ee133">Tricks of the Trade</content>
    <content contentuid="h6d7bb17cg089fg4642gb497gb147e6ab1dfb">Bard</content>
    <content contentuid="h6f4557b4gbcb9g4696ga5afg0fc01ddf893c">Drain Willpower</content>
    <content contentuid="h6f77e8f2g044eg44a8gacb8g64457aac8c8f">Whenever you damage a target, their resistance to that type of damage is reduced by an amount dependant on your Metamind score. In addition, [1] also increases the range of spells and scrolls by [2]m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;a6a6a6&quot;&gt;[1] can reduce a resistance by the following amounts, from Metamind level one to eight:&lt;br&gt;4, 8, 12, 17, 22, 28, 34, 40.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h78c6c9d2g4db6g4199g971dgae12fa5255a0"/>
    <content contentuid="h7a2f1a05g4b52g4ec2g8354g1f92a8bf442d">Arrows will inflict an additional 20% of their damage as bonus elemental damage depending on the surface your target is standing in.</content>
    <content contentuid="h809b87b4g868ag4e87gbe4bgb895f7efc47b">If you've been blinded, try to keep track of where everyone is before your turn. In Epic Encounters, blind characters have a difficult time seeing things.</content>
    <content contentuid="h80fde727ge4a2g43b4g89d6gcd5169b7c769"/>
    <content contentuid="h81ca938fg5ef4g452agb093g1294e2f0718b">During your turn, [1] consumes blood that you are standing in, healing you for 5% of your maximum vitality.</content>
    <content contentuid="h828f1b29ge3c9g4606gb942gf00216f796e2">In Epic Encounters your resistances are limited to 75%, but some powerful effects can allow you to surpass this limit.</content>
    <content contentuid="h83153759ge7a0g4db7gac47gd1096f9a5838">&lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Highlight&lt;/font&gt; an enemy and press [IE_ControllerContextMenu]. Select &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;'Examine'&lt;/font&gt;. Having more points in &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Lore Master&lt;/font&gt; reveals more &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;information&lt;/font&gt; on your &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;target&lt;/font&gt;.</content>
    <content contentuid="h844fc16bg7f56g43d7gb557g7035f62bffe7">Agonizing over how to build a character? Good! I accept the compliment.</content>
    <content contentuid="h8590f524g6455g48a4g8cdeg2806a597fd65">Shocking Arrow</content>
    <content contentuid="h8651dce9g1b1eg4627g96c3g173f38ff2ed2">Storm</content>
    <content contentuid="h86bee297g3f52g425egbef7g5057f1ee930d">Alchemist</content>
    <content contentuid="h8754c159gc32eg4f0dg8ef6g713745598108">Shocking Arrow</content>
    <content contentuid="h878c02c0gc629g470dg955cg80dc2a125cb2">[1] decreases everyone's attitude toward you by [2], but melee opponents will find you less attractive in combat. Additionally, whenever you enter combat, you attempt a free Sneak.</content>
    <content contentuid="h89605e46g90efg4577ga651g420a42678893">[1] improves your effectiveness with Poison damage, based on your Crafting score. Additionally, you can throw grenades [2] meters farther.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;a6a6a6&quot;&gt;Crafting 2: Once per round, your Poison damage can add one stack of Untreated Poison.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 3: You may stack Untreated Poison up to 4.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 4: If a target has no Untreated Poison stacks, your Poison damage applies one.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 5: You may stack Untreated Poison up to 5.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 6: If a target has less than Untreated Poison II, your Poison damage applies it.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 7: You may stack Untreated Poison up to 6.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 8: If a target has less than Untreated Poison III, your Poison damage applies it.&lt;br&gt;Crafting 9: Your Poison damage can add a stack of Untreated Poison up to 3 times each round.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Zombies are immune to Untreated Poison.</content>
    <content contentuid="h8981925fg4480g4807gabdegaae97cda602a">Chilling Arrow</content>
    <content contentuid="h8a265339ga358g4ae4ga309g439615cc79b1"/>
    <content contentuid="h8ddc8dd4ge8feg4420ga6dag0d87ce8ec743">[1] gives you 1 extra point of Perception and prevents enemies from performing attacks of opportunity on you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;[1] does not prevent attacks made due to Centurion or Predator.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h8fa27d2fgeb94g4475ga70ag1510273e6003">Master Assassin</content>
    <content contentuid="h8fbbcc05gdfedg47a6g890bg15fdc6e27028">[1] gives you physical resistance equal to your Soldier score times 3%. Also grants extra armour equal to your Soldier ability + [2].</content>
    <content contentuid="h9148ba3egc37cg4027gb92age3d08b69e419">Today a Wizard, tomorrow a Battlemage: Your starting stats don't have to determine the rest of your game. In Epic Encounters, you start with one respecialization point, and you can buy more from vendors- so don't be afraid to try new things!</content>
    <content contentuid="h91bcfee6g8442g4727g9b5dgfafae0d4608e">Violent</content>
    <content contentuid="h936ab728ga02dg4530ga964g42c293e43446">Ameranth's Trunks</content>
    <content contentuid="h996d0a05gbdf5g4413gb6b9g9208d085920f">[1] determines your luck in finding extra treasure, improves your Offence Rating by 3, Critical Chance by 1%, and gives you a chance to gain random benefits in combat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;At the start of each turn in combat, you have a chance to gain a random benefit. The chance of gaining an effect and the strength of the effect increase with a higher [1] score.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Level 1: 30%.&lt;br&gt;Level 2: 60%.&lt;br&gt;Level 3: 90%, 10% are strong.&lt;br&gt;Level 4: 100%, 30% are strong.&lt;br&gt;Level 5: 100%, 60% are strong.&lt;br&gt;Level 6: 100%, 60% are strong, 30% are exceptional.&lt;br&gt;Level 7: 100%, 40% are strong, 60% are exceptional.&lt;br&gt;Level 8: 100% chance for exceptional effect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Levels 9 and beyond grant a 30% chance to grant additional exceptional effect(s).&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h9b8fec02g2553g46c9gb3ecgcab7315f9e4f">[1] allows you to equip more powerful Tenebrium weapons and increases your maximum Tenebrium resistance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;Each point increases your maximum Tenebrium resistance by +1%.&lt;br&gt;Points above fifth increase maximum Tenebrium resistance by +2%.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="h9e932753g9e66g4a5eg88cage4336ae2d135"/>
    <content contentuid="h9fa58350g8f0cg4f8ag95fcg3b730d459602"/>
    <content contentuid="ha001e63dg4a1cg46deg9200g1fa7a48d3e0b"/>
    <content contentuid="ha04e7d1ag8bf6g4914g82a3gdb7efab194a3">Astrologer's Gaze</content>
    <content contentuid="ha231dd25gd2f6g4fcag8991gfedbefc7879c">Drain Willpower</content>
    <content contentuid="ha323378egb5f6g451cg858dged752a3540ca">[1] gives you the ability to perform one Attack of Opportunity, each round, with melee weapons.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;Attacks of Opportunity deal 30% increased damage and have additional benefits depending on the type of weapon you wield.&lt;br&gt;One-Handed: 100% chance to inflict Bleeding for 3 turns.&lt;br&gt;Two-handed: 100% chance to inflict Crippled for 2 turns.&lt;br&gt;Dagger: +1 Chain. &lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="ha39a1bbeg39a3g4f52g8953g8f2f6b6ee1fa">Pickpocketing</content>
    <content contentuid="ha43c6246g7c02g4281g8374g9cb63fbb2abf">With [1], your armour rating is increased by 6 times your Blacksmithing score. In addition, every time you hit or get hit, your gear has a [2]% chance of not losing durability.</content>
    <content contentuid="ha4c23394ge3d0g42d1ga894g577379e4e6f9">[1] grants you &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Stun&lt;/font&gt;.</content>
    <content contentuid="ha6e5ee5aga554g4f4cg8785gb0c60e78f4fd">[1] allows you to examine enemies, identify items, and move items from a distance.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="haa7cb1aag7092g4290g9179g9945743262f8">You've received Ameranth's Trunks.</content>
    <content contentuid="habf89ae8g71f1g4333gbf30gd36ed5463f9f"/>
    <content contentuid="hae52ff4bg54e7g4eabgb930gca752c4ba072">Physique</content>
    <content contentuid="haeacd961g8366g4afbga52agdc51c03b4570">Pesky Hyperacutes getting the better of your Rogue? Throw a blind on 'em and they won't spot much more after that.</content>
    <content contentuid="hb2647f59g3906g4b9bg8b96g0f3ce9518e07">Angel</content>
    <content contentuid="hb8aa942egbeaag4452gbfbcg31b493bead6e">Metamind</content>
    <content contentuid="hbb7a1718g390dg400agb5a4g9e07b758a2e8">Centurion</content>
    <content contentuid="hbb931846g8f68g45cdg9f97g45afae886797">Field Smith</content>
    <content contentuid="hbc6713f2gc8a4g4af7gb25dg71d4706d6059">Ameranth's Trunks</content>
    <content contentuid="hbd7fbc80g84d8g48c0gbf2cg33f27204e94c"/>
    <content contentuid="hc10e13b6gcb52g413bgaf14g6d725654e3e7">Make some mischief! Epic Encounters bundles Sneaking, Pickpocketing, and Lockpicking into one ability, Tricks of the Trade, so don't feel bad about grabbing a few points and terrorizing the townsfolk.</content>
    <content contentuid="hc20fac6bga77bg4662gb425g6ad74afc3878">[1] improves your saving throws against effects which test your presence of mind, arcane understanding, or strength of character.</content>
    <content contentuid="hc453e399ge1f5g41f1gaeabgcdd4de833c63">A character with [1] has +[2]% [3] and +[6]% maximum [3], but takes a [4]% penalty to [5]. Additionally, the character becomes able to perform a special [1] reaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;You start combat with zero of these reactions, but recover 1 at the start of each turn, storing up to 3. You can only perform [1] reactions when you would not be prevented from casting a spell, you can see your target, and it is not your turn.&lt;br&gt;You may only perform one of these actions at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demon reactions are performed against enemies within 20m who become Slowed, Cursed, or Weakened, dealing fire damage, Burning, and Poisoning.&lt;br&gt;Angel reactions are performed on allies within 20m who become Hastened, Blessed, or Fortified, healing 7% maximum vitality plus 2% per Intelligence beyond 10 and removing Burning and Weakened.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="hc6c2d08fgd8beg4b84g88e8ge696deeec37d">Loremaster level too low</content>
    <content contentuid="hc79c588bg8c5cg4e29g9c7fgb0d4d2c3108c">Many new skills have been added with Epic Encounters.&lt;br&gt;If you find a weird looking skillbook, it probably requires more than one ability to learn, but is well worth the investment.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcb3f875fg901eg406bg8ae3g315c4fa67509">[1] allows you to begin combat with two stored reactions for each ability or talent you have that provides reactions. Additionally, you are immune to environmental weather effects.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcb8f9837gdf0fg4a01ga7d6g5ed522b74189">[1] grants 1 extra point in Dexterity and allows you to flee combat even when enemies are right next to you. Additionally, grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Slowed&lt;/font&gt; with Scoundrel or Ranger 5.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcc42ecefg5965g48b7g98a1g2e34fb174186">[1] gives you +[2]% Elemental Resistance and +1% maximum Elemental Resistance per point in Soldier.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcfaa4c64g2a5dg4e36gb175g8ecbc1fcaa98">[1] gives you 4 extra Ability Points to spend.</content>
    <content contentuid="hcfee1aeag363eg421fgb230g54c60be6d596">Empowered skills are improved variants of existing skills that can only appear on equipment.&lt;br&gt;You can always see which part of the skill is altered by looking for &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;colored text&lt;/font&gt; on the skill card.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd0c4c763gc5deg4381gb73eg59493fa5232b">[1] decreases everyone's attitude towards you by [2] but gives you [3] extra point in [4]. Additionally, grants &lt;font color=&quot;00ffff&quot;&gt;immunity to Blind&lt;/font&gt; with Witchcraft 5.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd2bafc20g2692g4ac2g8c9cg957d3c671850">Cobalt</content>
    <content contentuid="hd2d18f3fg37d4g49d3ga9eagdfbea2eacd0c">If a fight is getting the better of you, don't feel bad- this stuff is pretty hard. You can always flee and come back when you're more prepared, too- but let's be real; who flees?</content>
    <content contentuid="hd30ded14g5ad5g4712gbf66g32736faa955f">Be sure to pay Epic Encounters' additional areas a visit. You can find the entrace to this content from the later portion of the Phantom Forest- it's tough to miss.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd35d8840g085ag445cg9f1ag3ea6c9d590cc">&lt;font color=8e3f8e&gt;Lowered Resistances&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="hd5795b3fgc483g4dc8g86d8g46f8a376c739">Bows and crossbows have the potential to fire from great distances, but are always limited to your sight radius and become less accurate when further from a target.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd5e6d946ge66cg4a34ga8c6gcd3500e27704">Many skills have higher &quot;recommended&quot; attribute or ability values than their requirements. In Epic Encounters, you can always see these values on any skill or skillbook.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd749731fgb0cdg42a4g8133g6f2b8385b005">A character with [1] moves at normal speed while sneaking and can gain 1 additional Chain stack per turn.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd75d5dc6g93dcg4e64gb6abgc5b09e3cd52b">Chilling Arrowhead</content>
    <content contentuid="hd7c21999g602cg4497gaa65g41507b81eda1">[1] increases your Turn Action Points and Maximum Action Points by +1 for every missing 10% of Vitality below 50%.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd872ac87gd70ag45d7g9726ga4397fd776b0">Shocking Arrowhead</content>
    <content contentuid="hd8c70f78g43eeg44c9g81f2gcf16132b1e21">Nimble</content>
    <content contentuid="hd955c0d8g5b89g4b04gab49gae16a6b5e620">Highlight an enemy and press [IE_ContextMenu] and select &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;'Examine'&lt;/font&gt;. The higher your &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Loremaster&lt;/font&gt; ability, the more you get to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;know&lt;/font&gt; about your target.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd9836a03gdb10g42a9g9cc6g74aa3f86c6b9">[1] determines the first impression you make on other people and your talent for Charming, Intimidating, and Reasoning. In combat, you may perform Bardic reactions to various situations when it is not your turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;9d9c9c&quot;&gt;The amount of Bardic reactions you can make each round, as well as the power and variety of those reactions, depends on your [1] score.&lt;br&gt;You start combat with no reactions, but recover up to 2 at the start of your turn, storing those that go unused.&lt;br&gt;Every level of Bard that does not improve the power of your reactions increases your maximum stored reaction amount by 1.&lt;br&gt;At 4th and 7th level, your Bardic reactions improve.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First Tier Triggers: An ally misses an attack, becomes Burning, becomes Frozen, becomes Stunned, or becomes Petrified. An enemy scores a critical hit, or becomes Hasted.&lt;br&gt;Second Tier Triggers: An ally slips on ice, becomes Feared, becomes Slowed, or blocks an attack. An enemy blocks an attack.&lt;br&gt;Third Tier Triggers: An ally becomes Charmed or loses Invisibility or Sneaking out of turn.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="hd9bfb323g2f59g48c2gbd9dg906a8374a223"/>
    <content contentuid="hd9df7e13ge3d4g4aabga798g7caabc9f9f27">Tricks of the Trade governs the three roguish abilities of Sneaking, Lockpicking, and Pickpocketing.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="hdab2ce7bg0527g486cg9796g97bf861a5875"/>
    <content contentuid="hdadd9969g6bd6g41dcgb943g0b297855c48d"/>
    <content contentuid="hdb52268eg0ea9g458dg9cb7ge34ecc146760">[1] increases all damage while invisible by 20%, and increases attack damage while sneaking by [2]%.</content>
    <content contentuid="hde0b6c08g84aag4d01g81f0g6fb72e073a90">You've found an &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Identifying Glass&lt;/font&gt;! If your &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;Loremaster&lt;/font&gt; ability is high enough you'll be able to &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;identify&lt;/font&gt; items. Press [IE_ContextMenu] on the &lt;font color=&quot;70b10e&quot;&gt;unidentified&lt;/font&gt; item and select 'Identify'.</content>
    <content contentuid="hdebdc54fg082dg4973ga6e8g54695c64fb9a">Inconspicuous</content>
    <content contentuid="hdf8e7f7eg7880g42e7gac90gaed20ec6f948">[1] increases your Movement Speed by 20% and your Initiative by 4.</content>
    <content contentuid="he1a8eb0eg277fg4278gaa18g1dc22e1cc830">Even if someone really deserves it, murder in broad daylight is sure to be an entertaining experience.</content>
    <content contentuid="he62f6b57g6b2cg4d84gb473g349491be8224">You can move heavy items by increasing your Strength or investing points in Metamind.</content>
    <content contentuid="he8b593b1g2187g47f6g9424g063cb6b60789">Reaper</content>
    <content contentuid="hea860e3ag9226g41a8ga17bg0a997bf896fa">Hyperacuity</content>
    <content contentuid="hedae705dg3f1cg44dfg88f1gd8de8c72963d">Level [1]: Boosts Initiative by 9, Damage by 10%, Chance to hit by 10%, Critical Chance by 3%, Armour Rating by 10, Grants Immunity to Fear, and adds +1 to Willpower.&lt;br&gt;</content>
    <content contentuid="hf0e4bfb0gb6d6g4700g9801gb21d26cc8ffc">Many skills have a reduced character level requirement in Epic Encounters, so go ahead and experiment with all that top-shelf stuff early on. Besides, you'll probably need it anyway.</content>
    <content contentuid="hf1cbbfacg4f75g4e8cg93c1ga7072fc4aa07">Epic Encounters introduces several ways to perform various reactions while out of turn.&lt;br&gt;These are similar to Attacks of Opportunity, but trigger in different ways and have a wide range of effects.</content>
    <content contentuid="hf53604d5g41a8g4c4eg9550g09e5b8eff2a7"/>
    <content contentuid="hf647658fg2f25g41feg8f17g269b1dbd998b">Ranger</content>
    <content contentuid="hf66531fcg8dc0g42b7gbbe8g9c0ef90959cb">In Epic Encounters spears are classified as Dexterity weapons- so go ahead, be the next Oberyn! Just try to keep a cool head.</content>
    <content contentuid="hfe4293e9g08c6g4194ga0c8g4a29b269a2e6">Chilling Arrow</content>
    <content contentuid="hfeb6836cgdd51g4381g9f59gb01bb91f5036"/>
</contentList>
